cricketershop.com 2017-06-06

# Secure shopping at Cricketer Shop | Safe & Dependable Online Cricket Shop | Buy with confidence

  Loading... Please wait...

Cricketershop.com and its affiliates, respect your Privacy. Please read below policy carefully about the collection, usage anddissemination of the personal information that is provided by you and collected by us from you site usage. Please note that wereserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time without notice and you should read it periodically.

**Collection of Information:** We may collect the Information , which is provided by you during the registering process and alsocollect it anonymously with your user data on our site.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information:** We use this information to process your requests, your orders and to respond toyou in the normal process of our service. We may also use this information to contact you or to make marketing offers to you.

We use your PII for our internal purposes only and do not rent, trade or share your personal information with any other companyfor marketing purposes without your prior consent. We however, reserve the right to share your personal information with anythird party, including law enforcement which makes a legally compliant request for its disclosure.

We also reserve the right to share your personal information with other third parties for prevention of financial fraud, illegalactivities, security and for safeguarding of our legal rights.

Sometimes, we may need to procure a service or a component of service from a third party or a service provider. In those case,primarily to provide the service to you, we may need to disclose your personal information. Under the provisions of this PrivacyPolicy, you agree for such usage of your personal information.

**Modifications to your PII:** You may modify your personal information at any time. You also can choose to be removed fromour mailing lists and/or to cancel your registration. In the event of cancellation of your registration, the data will stored in thearchive folders of our servers.

**Collection and Use of Demographic and Profile Data:** In addition to the personal information provided to us by you, we willalso collect your user activity data on our site. This may be collected by the use of “cookies” and other such technological means.This data is used to enhance, customize and personalize the site content and to tailor marketing efforts for the users of particularprofiles. It’s also used to track user activity and to understand and improve user experience. We may disclose and share thisinformation to a third party, however in a form that is aggregated and not personally identifiable to you.

**Disclaimer on Security of Personal Information:** Every effort will be made by us to safeguard your personal information andits confidentiality. However, transmissions of information on the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be absolutely safe. By usingour site and services, you agree for this limited risk and will not hold us or any of our affiliates liable for any loss to you causedby acts of any third party.

**Security of Payment :** The payments are processed by CCAvenue Payment gateways and they used the latest encryptiontechnology to protect your financial information.
